guitarampkeyboard.com 2009-02-27

# Privacy Policy

| ****  
  
The following statement explains our policy regarding the personal information we collect about you.

Introduction   
Visitor Information   
What is a cookie?   
Submitting personal information   
Access to your personal information   
Users 16 and under   
How to find and control your cookies   
How do you know which sites use cookies?   
How to see your cookie code

1\. Introduction   
This policy covers the GAK’s use of personal information that the GAK collects when you use GAK.co.uk. The policy also gives you information about cookies; GAK's use of cookies; and how you may reject such cookies. 

From time to time, you will be asked to submit personal information about yourself (e.g. name and email address) in order to receive or use services on our website. Such services may include newsletters, online shopping, GAK.co.uk account memberships. 

By entering your details in the fields requested, you enable the GAK to provide you with the services you select. Whenever you provide such personal information, we will treat that information in accordance with this policy. When using your personal information GAK will act in accordance with current legislation and aim to meet current Internet best practice. 

2\. Visitor Information   
During the course of any visit to GAK.co.uk, the pages you see, along with a short text file called a 'cookie', are downloaded to your computer. Many websites do this, because cookies enable website publishers to do useful things like find out whether the computer (and probably its user) has visited the website before. This is done on a repeat visit by checking to see, and finding, the cookie left there on the last visit. 

Information supplied by cookies can help us to provide you with a better online user experience and assist us to analyse the profile of our visitors.   
[Top]

3\. What is a cookie?   
A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. 

Many sites do this whenever a user visits their website in order to track online traffic flows. 

Cookies record information about your online preferences. Users have the opportunity to set their computers to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. The last of these, of course, means that certain personalised services cannot then be provided to that user user and accordingly you may not be able to take full advantage of all of the GAK.co.uk features. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. 

If you have set your computer to reject cookies you can still browse GAK.co.uk anonymously until such time as you wish to register for GAK.co.uk services or decide to use the online shopping service. For further information on cookies please visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).   
[Top]

4\. Use and storage of your personal information   
When you supply any personal information to GAK.co.uk (e.g. for GAK account membership) we have legal obligations towards you in the way we use those data. We must collect the information fairly, that is, we must explain how we will use it (see the notices on particular webpages that let you know why we are requesting the information) and tell you if we want to pass the information on to anyone else. 

In general, any information you provide to the GAK will only be used within the GAK and by its agents. Your information will be disclosed where we are obliged or permitted by law. Also, if you post or send offensive, inappropriate or objectionable content anywhere on or to GAK.co.uk or otherwise engage in any disruptive behaviour on GAK.co.uk, the GAK can use whatever information that is available to it about you to stop such behaviour. This may involve informing relevant third parties such as your employer, school e-mail/Internet provider and law enforcement agencies about the content and your behaviour. 

We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as you use the service you have requested, and remove it in the event that the purpose has been met, or, in the case of GAK.co.uk membership you no longer wish to continue your registration as a GAK.co.uk member. For safety reasons, however, the GAK may store messaging transcript data (including message content, member names, times and dates) arising from the use of GAK.co.uk services such as the FAQs. Where personal information is held for people who are not yet registered but have taken part in other GAK.co.uk services (e.g. online services), that information will be held as long as is necessary to ensure that the service is run smoothly. We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. 

If you are notified on a GAK.co.uk site that your information may be used to allow the GAK to contact you for "service administration purposes", this means that the GAK may contact you for a number of purposes related to the service you have signed up for.   
[Top]

5\. Access to your personal information   
You have the right to request a copy of the personal information the GAK holds about you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. (There may be a charge of up to £10 for information requests.) Please address requests to the Data Protection Officer, 30 Cheapside, Brighton BN1 4AG (Email: mail@gak.co.uk).   
[Top]

6\. Users 16 and under   
If you are aged 16 or under, please get your parent/guardian's permission beforehand whenever you provide personal information to the GAK's website. Users without this consent are not allowed to provide us with personal information.   
[Top]

7\. How to find and control your cookies   
If you're using Netscape 6.0:   
On your Task Bar, click:   
Edit, then   
Preferences   
Click on Advanced   
Click on Cookies   
If you're using Internet Explorer 6.0:   
Choose Tools, then   
Internet Options   
Click the Privacy Tab   
Click on Custom Level   
Click on the 'Advanced' button   
Check the 'override automatic cookie handing' box and select Accept, Block or Prompt for action as appropriate.   
If you're using Internet Explorer 5.0 or 5.5:   
Choose Tools, then   
Internet Options   
Click the Security tab   
Click on Custom Level   
Scroll down to the sixth option to see how cookies are handled by IE5 and change to Accept, Disable, or Prompt for action as appropriate.   
If you're using Internet Explorer 4.0:   
Choose View, then   
Internet Options   
Click the Advanced tab   
Scroll down to the yellow exclamation icon under Security and choose one of the three options to regulate your use of cookies.   
If you're using Internet Explorer 3.0:   
You can View, Options, Advanced, then click on the button that says Warn before Accepting Cookies. 

If you're using Netscape Communicator 4.0:   
On your Task Bar, click:   
Edit, then   
Preferences   
Click on Advanced   
Set your options in the box that says Cookies.   
[Top]

8\. How do you know which of the sites you've visited use cookies?   
If you're using Netscape 6.0:   
On your Task Bar, click:   
Edit, then   
Preferences   
Click on Advanced   
Click on Cookies   
Click the View Cookies button   
If you're using Internet Explorer 5.0 or 6.0:   
Choose Tools, then   
Internet Options   
Click the General tab   
Click Settings   
View Files   
If you're using Internet Explorer 4.0:   
On your Task Bar, click:   
View, then   
Internet Options   
Under the tab General (the default tab) click   
Settings   
View Files.   
If you're using Internet Explorer 3.0:   
On your Task Bar, click:   
View   
Options   
Advanced   
View Files.   
If you're using Netscape Communicator 4.0:   
Netscape bundles all cookies into one file on your hard drive. You'll need to find the file, which it calls Cookie.txt on Windows machines. [Top]

9\. How to see your cookie code   
Just click on a cookie to open it. You'll see a short string of text and numbers. The numbers are your identification card, which can only be seen by the server that gave you the cookie. [Top]

GAK.CO.UK LTD © 2001-2006   
60 Gladstone Place   
Brighton,   
BN2 3QD

 ****  
OFFICIALLY THE UKs NO 1 GIBSON DEALER!   
PRS Guitars @ GAK !!!   
GAK SUPPORTS GUITAR IDOL 2009!   
TC ELECTRONIC REBEL BASS STACK   
EPIPHONE LES PAULS IN STOCK NOW !!   
Rode NT-1a MEGA DEAL !   
The Ultimate Mackie SRM-450 Deal.   
Vox Valvetronix   
Alesis DM 5 Kit Pro FREE Drum Throne Megadeal

Errors & omissions excepted, © Copyright 2002-2009 GAK.CO.UK LTD

| | Account Login  
---  
  
E-mail  
  
Password  

 Sign up now  
 Privacy Policy  

 Rotosound Steve Harris Signature Set 50 75 95 110  
£  
CHEAP DELIVERY !  (From £)  
  
 Ibanez ATK700  
£  
 _FREE_ DELIVERY !!!  
  
 S.E. Electronics SE-2200a  
£  
CHEAP DELIVERY !  (From £)  
  
 ESP F-10 Pack  
£  
  
 Tapco S-5CHEAP DELIVERY !  (From £)  
  
 Gretsch G6120SSC Brian Setzer Tribute ONE ONLY !!  
£  
  
 Rockbass Streamer Std 4 - 1 pickup  
£  
  
 Hartke Kickback 15  
£  
 _FREE_ DELIVERY !!!  
[](https://seal.verisign.com/splash?form_file=fdf/splash.fdf&dn=WWW.GUITARAMPKEYBOARD.COM&lang=en)| Browse  
---  

AKG  
Ahead  
Akai  
Alesis  
Ampeg  
Art  
Audio-Tech  
Behringer  
Boss  
Brian May  
Cakewalk  
D'Addario  
Danelectro  
Dean  
Digidesign  
Digitech  
Dunlop  
E Bow  
E-Mu  
EMG  
ESP  
Earthwood  
Edirol  
E/Harmonix  
Elites  
Elixir  
Epiphone  
Ernie Ball  
Evans  
Fender  
Fishman  
GHS  
Gator  
Gibraltar  
Gibson  
Guitar Tech  
Guvnor  
Hercules  
Hiscox  
Hosa  
Ibanez  
JBL  
Jack Daniels  
Jackson  
Jim Dunlop  
Korg  
Kyser  
Laney  
Levys  
Line6  
M-Audio  
MXR  
Mackie  
Mapex  
Marshall  
Martin  
Meinl  
Orange  
Paiste  
Pearl  
Peavey  
Pikcard  
Planet Waves  
Pro - Mark  
Protection R  
Quik-Lok  
Remo  
Rode  
Roland  
Rotosound  
S.I.T  
Sabian  
Samson  
Schaller  
Sennheiser  
Seymour Dunc  
Shubb  
Shure  
Skull String  
Squier  
Stagg  
String Swing  
TC Helicon  
Tama  
Tapco  
Tascam  
Ultimate  
Vater  
Venom  
Vic Firth  
Vintage  
Vox  
Warwick  
Rockbag  
Washburn  
Whirlwind  
Wise Publica  
Yamaha  
Zildjian  
Zoom  

If you see cheaper prices we will match any genuine quote
